marina
marina
me fame Well it has taken its
yo la fama Pues me ha pasado bastante
toll on me the truth not very well Well
factura la verdad no muy bien Bueno la
beautiful people no not very well I'm really
gente bonita no no muy bien de verdad te
telling you no Javi Turn off the fan because
lo digo no Javi Apaga el ventilador que
the peels move a lot Today
las que las cáscaras se mueven mucho Hoy
we are funny with my appearance
estamos graciosos con mi apariencia
look at you if she is messing with me
fíjate tú si se está metiendo conmigo
for putting a banana Imagine if they had
por poner un plátano Imagínate si me
seen me with the real appearance that I have
hubieran con la apariencia real que
right now Well I think
tengo en estos momentos Bueno yo creo
Pili has seen me I don't know if she has
que Pili me ha visto no sé si me ha
seen me but well if she hasn't seen me better so I
visto pero bueno si no me ha visto mejor
can sleep peacefully today
para para que pueda dormir tranquila hoy
a kiss Pili you are loved very much Pili
un beso Pili se te quiere muchísimo Pili
beautiful you know why I tell you about
bonita sabes por qué te digo lo de la
fame not with this that you are viral now
fama no con esto de que eres viral ahora
and well anyway Then what a mistake What a
y bueno en fin Entonces qué error Qué
horror No man I want to be calm
horror No hombre quiero estar tranquila
in a field and that nobody flour snals
en un campo y que nadie harina snals se
has gone viral Hey please Well you
ha viralizado Oye por favor Bueno tú
too both of you both together yes
también los dos los dos juntitos sí
Well but I go out there because I am handsome next to it
Bueno pero yo salgo ahí por guapo al
I come out a little bit of filler But
lado yo salga yo un poco de relleno Pero
if you notice the whole dedication is to you
si te fijas toda la dedicatoria es a ti
eh Look at this girl this girl I love
eh Mira esta chica esta chica me encanta
and her opinion on the rubiales and
y su opinión sobre lo de rubiales y la
Jenny and the common Jenny she like
Jenny y la Jenny común ella como
anyone who has  eyes and ears has
cualquiera que tenga ojos y oídos ha
said what happened the videos the laughter
dicho lo que pasó los vídeos las risas
of the players in the locker room the
de las jugadoras en el vestuario las
statements on the day of the World Cup and how he
declaraciones el día del mundial y como
later changed his version of
luego ha cambiado su versión de los
events those who say otherwise just
hechos quienes digan lo contrario solo
to look good in the face of the radical feminist wave
para quedar bien ante la ola feminista
are cowards or hypocrites
radical son cobardes y o hipócritas
we are talking about that this video right
estamos hablando de que este vídeo en
now has pay attention eh it
este momento tiene atentos eh
's here Ah no it's not the same
está aquí Ah no no es el mismo capitán
naughty captain it's not the same no Ah no no no
travieso no es el mismo no Ah no
no captain of the thirds captain
no no no capitán de los tercios capitán
of the thirds Well then this tweet
de los tercios Bueno pues este tweet
this video that we are going to remember
este vídeo que vamos a recordar
this clip has right now almost a
este clip tiene ahora mismo casi un
million views on Twitter Marines
millón de visitas en Twitter Marines
for his forceful statements and his
por su contundentes declaraciones y su
firm opinion on the subject Jenny
firme opinión sobre el tema Jenny
Hermosillo
Hermosillo
Exactly the same scared because I have been
Exactamente igual acojonada porque Llevo
watching social networks for a few days watching
viendo las redes sociales viendo los
television programs and yesterday I
programas de televisión y ayer lo
was commenting on it I was commenting on it with a friend
comentaba lo comentaba con con un amigo
and I say they are managing to
y digo están consiguiendo
make me doubt some things that my
hacerme dudar de algunas cosas que mi
common sense
sentido común
tells me that it is an outrage
me dice que es que es una barbaridad
everything that I am experiencing in the sense
todo lo que estoy viviendo en el sentido
of to me this gentleman Rubiales the little
de a mí el señor este rubiales lo poco
that I knew in front of him is of all this
que conocía delante es de todo este
scandal that apart from that I think it is being
escándalo que aparte que creo que se
used  to cover up what is
está utilizando para tapar lo
truly important, which is that I
verdaderamente importante que es que yo
go to the supermarket and a liter
voy al supermercado y me cuesta el litro
of oil costs me 7 €, gasoline is about 70,
de aceite 7 € la gasolina está a unos 70
where is it, how is the government, or
que dónde está cómo está el gobierno o
rather, what political panorama do we have in Spain?
sea que panorama tenemos político España
Everything important is being covered up with
todo lo importante se está tapando con
this case, the fact itself, the fact itself
este caso que el hecho en sí el hecho en
that is being unloaded seems
sí que se está descargando me parece
absurd to me, something else seems much worse to me
absurdo otra cosa me parece mucho peores
related to this issue, yesterday it came out
de relacionadas con ese tema ayer sale
yesterday, however, this thing came out that catches my
ayer sin embargo sale eso que me llama
attention and what really offends me is
la atención y lo que realmente me ofende
that a person who benefits from
que una persona que sea beneficiado de
the law, the law only if he tries to
la ley de la ley solo sí es sí intenta
rape a girl, is left in the
violar a una chica queda en un segundo
background, are totally relegated, some great
plano queda totalmente relegado unas
players that I have been
pedazo de jugadoras que yo llevo toda mi
playing soccer all my life, who are always
vida jugando al fútbol que está siempre
playing with boys, I love
jugando con chicos que amo el fútbol
women's soccer and I wish I had had the
femenino y que ojalá yo hubiera tenido
opportunity that they have had and it
la oportunidad que han tenido ellas y me
seems to me that they have won a
parece unas creas que han ganado un
world cup, I was moved and how it has been
mundial que me emocioné y que cómo se ha
used, it has been politicized and how all of
utilizado se ha politizado y como todas
them have fallen, the majority in this game,
ellas han caído la mayoría en este juego
analyzing everything, watching all the
que analizando todo viendo todos los
videos, it seems to me that I am at home
vídeos me parece estoy en mi casa
stunned, reading the networks saying this
atónita leyendo las redes diciendo esto
is a joke, I mean
es una broma o sea gente que considera
people who consider themselves intelligent with false morals, a hypocrisy that I have spoken to in person and then on television you see them saying the opposite because that is what must be said because if not they will lynch you and they will be left without hair that is why I am here on YouTube I am happy because I am
yo aquí en YouTube Soy feliz porque soy
free and on television they are not and I do not know
libre y en televisión no lo son y no sé
how they can fake an argument say
cómo pueden fingir un argumento decir
something that they really do not feel okay to me
algo que realmente no sienten vale a mí
the blond is this I fall like ass I
el rubial es este Me cae como el culo me
think he is a fool I think he is a
parece un baboso me parece un
crook he has been good yes he has been
chanchullero ha sido bueno si ha sido
corrupt No I do not have to say it
corrupto No yo no tengo por qué decirlo
the gesture that he made with his balls
el gesto que hizo ese con los huevos me
disgusts me I forgot to mention that
da asco se me olvidó comentar eso
for God's sake I am disgusted but but specifically
por Dios me asco pero pero concretamente
yes totally disgusting or whatever or whatever I
sí totalmente asqueroso o sea como o sea
also tell you also I tell you mine but
también te digo también te digo mío pero
but specifically the issue of the peak It is
pero concretamente el tema del pico Es
that I really also How have the events
que yo de verdad además Cómo ha
occurred or rather how have the
transcurrido o sea cómo transcurrido los
events occurred that if you get up that if not that
acontecimientos que si te levantas que
yes when we clearly see in
si no que sí cuando vemos claramente en
those images What are you doing I
esas imágenes Qué estás haciendo Te
can give you a peak such we give him I say Well maybe it
puedo dar un pico tal le damos digo Pues
was out of place or
a lo mejor estaba fuera de lugar o a lo
maybe I obviously would not have taken
mejor yo evidentemente no lo hubiera
note  But you can see perfectly how
hecho nota Pero se ve perfectamente como
the other one comes out laughing like later in the
la otra sale se ríe como luego en el
locker room there is a video where they are
vestuario hay un video donde están
talking about the wedding with blondes they are
hablando la boda con rubiales están
all laughing hahaha you liked it well
descojonando todas jijiji te gustó pues
no Well not much but I don't know what hahaha I
no Pues no mucho pero no sé qué Jajaja O
mean they are absolutely breaking up in
sea se están partiendo absolutamente en
the box of the situation as the plan is
la caja de la situación como el plan es
surreal it's a joke But at no
surrealista es de coña Pero en ningún
time is there any affection of any kind and
momento hay un afecto de ningún tipo y
more when two days later you are going to
más cuando los dos días te estás yendo a
Ibiza you put on a decal Arroyo
Ibiza te pones una calcamonía Arroyo
provocation of
provocación de
without summer there is no kiss etc etc etc that is
sin verano no hay beso etc etc etc que
clearly seen
se ve claramente
How are we but listen to me How are we
Cómo estamos pero escúchame Cómo estamos
classifying it as aggression is that it seems
catalogando de agresión es que me parece
offensive to me for people with common sense
ofensivo para las personas con sentido
aggression I am reading I see the
agresión yo estoy leyendo veo el
analysis right But more people intelligent people
análisis verdad Pero a más gente gente
but the thing is that in the end without wanting to they make you
pero es que al final sin querer te hacen
not empathize with him but rather the other
no empatizar con él sino que el otro te
generates a rejection in you because because 200
genere un rechazo yo porque porque 200
people on Twitter tell me that I have to
personas en Twitter me digan que tengo
say this because it seems that they
que decir esto porque es que parece que
are not imposing that we have to
no están imponiendo que tenemos que
say what they want us to say
decir lo que ellos quieren que digan
this girl releases a statement a
esta chica saca un comunicado un
statement in which I believe she is
comunicado en el que yo creo que está
advised by x and a  feminism
asesorada por x y un feminismo el
feminism brave feminism but
feminismo bravo el feminismo pero es que
this is not feminism or rather this is a
esto no es feminismo o sea esto es una
way of
manera de
how they are making me
cómo es que me están haciendo que coja
reject women's football because
rechazo al fútbol femenino porque la
attention has been diverted to this issue but they
atención se ha desviado a este tema pero
have diverted it I said the other day on
la han desviado decía el otro día la
TV is that now we have to be
tele es que ahora tenemos que estar
talking about this instead of You the
hablando de esto en vez Vosotros los
media they all of them are the ones who
medios ellos todos ellos son los que
are making us talk about
están haciendo que estemos hablando de
this [ __ ] shitty Absurd issue instead
esta [__] [__] Absurda de tema en vez
of focusing on how these people have
de centrarnos en que estas personas han
achieved great things they are the ones who
conseguido grande ellos son los que
are constantly stopping the image of the
están parando todo el rato la imagen del
peak stopped as if they were stuck together
pico parada como Si estuvieran pegados
as if he were him it is disgusting but in
como si él fuera él es asqueroso pero en
itself the gesture seems to me or rather what I read
sí el gesto me parece o sea lo que leo
on the networks and what I see on television and
en redes y lo que veo en televisión y
the arguments and on social networks it
los argumentos y en redes sociales me
seems to me like a frustrated people of a
parece de una gente frustrada de una
sick people that I say we are
gente enferma que yo digo se nos está
going crazy and this society
yendo la pinza y a mí esta sociedad me
scares me and that does not mean supporting the
da miedo y eso no significa apoyar al
other because I repeat I am disgusted that guy in
otro porque repito Me dasco ese tío en
general generates rejection in me look
general me genera rechazo fíjate tú que
at the specific issue of the peak the
en el asunto concreto del pico la
magnitude and the How the flock  How
magnitud y el Cómo el rebaño el Cómo la
public opinion and pressure is
opinión pública y la presión
exerted on the media, that is, the
se ejerce sobre los medios o sea los
media exerts pressure on
medios de comunicación ejercen sobre
all people in general, on networks, on
toda la gente en general de redes sobre
the population and they make you feel like if you
la población y como que te hacen sentir
don't say that you're [ __ ], a
que si no dices eso eres una [__] un
sexist hasn't even been left out, such a thing is that it
machista aún no se quedó un tal es que
even makes you doubt, it has even made
te hace hasta dudar me ha hecho hasta
me doubt and I say, are we going
dudar a mí y digo nos estamos volviendo
crazy? It's that it gives me It's that I'm really
locos Es que me da Es que de verdad te
telling you, it's that it scares me and I don't care to
lo digo es que me da miedo y me da igual
say it here that I'm worse No because I'm
decirlo aquí que soy peor No porque soy
clear and I'm sincere, man, and
clara y soy sincera tío y
totally How good Hey, but you told me
totalmente Qué bueno Oye pero me dijiste
that the kids hadn't uploaded this, they didn't
que esto no habían subido los niños no
upload excerpts of this, I
subieron extractos de esto
think you don't know what's going on, I say, you'll
creo que no sabes lo que pasa yo digo ya
see what's going to happen to me and it gives me But
verás la que me va a caer y me da Pero
the truth is that it hasn't been No, the truth is
la verdad es que no ha sido No la verdad
that almost everything has been positive and I don't care
que casi todo ha sido positivo y me da
because it seems that as soon as you say
igual porque parece que en cuanto dices
this, automatically, good, good you are, did
esto ya automáticamente bueno bueno eres
n't the kids release excerpts of
no sacaron los chavales extractos de
this, it's that clear, let's see, I think
esto es que claro a ver creo que no
we're not on Twitter and these people haven't
vamos en Twitter y esta gente no han
released excerpts, I think not And look,
sacado extracto creo que no Y fíjate que
from what I said here, I reaffirm myself
de esto que dije aquí es que me reafirmo
a lot now  more So today I don't do them
ahora mucho más O sea que hoy no los
the kids do it, they upload it for me
hago yo lo hacen los chavales me lo
and when I've been away these days they've
suben y cuando he estado estos días
taken care of
fuera pues se han encargado de ellos de
their bi-strata and so on But how good eh
su biestratos y demás Pero qué bueno eh
How good no no but it's not the only
Qué bueno no no pero no es la única
account that has posted your clip there are several
cuenta que ha puesto tu clip hay varias
accounts that have posted yours but let's
cuentas que han puesto tu pero vamos a
see not even if I were here one I don't know an
ver ni que yo fuera aquí una no sé una
erudite You're welcome I mean really it's like
erudita De nada o sea realmente es como
the typical opinion on the street is that not
la típica opinión de la calle es que ni
even journalistically is it having a
siquiera periodísticamente es tener un
bit of common sense which I think
poco de sentido común que creo que
exists more and more luckily there are a lot of
cada vez existe por suerte hay muchísima
people and above all the people on the street
gente y sobre todo la gente de la calle
in general I think they see it a bit like that
en general creo que lo ve un poco así
but you go into social networks you
pero entras en redes sociales
turn on television you watch the
pones la televisión ves los medios de
media to which I belong and
comunicación a los que yo pertenezco y
I sincerely feel like an outsider
yo sinceramente me siento una extraña
but not because I am in any way
pero no porque yo sea ni muchísimo menos
superior or in any way anything but
superior ni muchísimo menos nada sino
when I say what I say
que cuando digo lo de
The false morality and the hypocrisy
como digo La falsa moral y la hipocresía
is because I have spoken with several
es porque yo he hablado con varios
colleagues with several colleagues that I
compañeros con varios compañeros que yo
understand that many of them inform and
entiendo que muchos de ellos informan y
have to inform and tell the facts
tienen que informar y contar los hechos
themselves regardless of whether there are
en sí independientemente de que haya en
programs or formats in which
programas o en formatos que se omiten
some are omitted  parts but when we get
algunas partes pero ya cuando entramos
into the discussion groups when it comes to giving our opinions
en tertulianos a la hora de opinar
I've heard I'm not going to name
yo he escuchado tampoco no voy a dar
names obviously but I've
nombres evidentemente pero yo he
heard colleagues that I've
escuchado compañeros con los que he
spoken to who have said to me Joe Marina
hablado que me han dicho Joe Marina si
yes how can this be done
es que cómo se puede estar haciendo esto
but literally eh to a person what is it that
pero literal eh en una persona que tal
then I if this is
que es que entonces yo si esto es
considered sexual assault
considerado una agresión sexual
I have been sexually assaulted 200
Yo he sido agredida sexualmente 200.000
billion times understand me for God I mean
millones de veces entendedme por Dios o
come on it's that it's that it's that
sea vamos es que o sea es que
please it seems to me
es que es que por favor es que me parece
and colleagues telling me is that I can't
y compañeros diciéndome es que no me
believe How a person is being criminalized
puedo creer Cómo se está criminalizando
and
y
publicly murdered who
asesinando públicamente a una persona
maybe has a million
que a lo mejor tiene un millón de
reasons to have been
motivos para que se le haya asesino
publicly murdered some time ago for a thousand and one
públicamente tiempo atrás por mil y una
things is that he has done and I repeat this gesture
cosa es que haya hecho y repito el gesto
that he made in the box it seemed so
este que hizo en el palco me pareció tan
disgusting to me what he did that I have
asqueroso lo que haya hecho que me he
investigated a little about his
investigado un poco sobre su vida
previous life and things that I have read and that
anterior y cosas que he leído y que han
fellow journalists have been bringing out
ido sacando compañeros periodistas
Over the last few years scandals that he has
Durante los últimos años escándalos que
had Uff it gives me like
ha tenido Uff me da como
regardless of whether I know more or
independientemente que yo sepa más o
less I say Uff it gives me  He's a person
sepa menos digo Uff me da es una persona
who doesn't generate any kind of
que no me genera en ningún tipo de
empathy in me and no kind of
empatía y ningún tipo de
in fact I see him as, I mean, I see him from a
de hecho le veo como o sea le veo de un
profile
perfil
against, I mean, let's see, against, like
en contra de O sea a ver en contra como
you don't think the kiss is that serious, I mean, not
que no te parezca tan grave lo del beso
at all, let's see, it's not that big a deal, it
o sea para nada a ver que no es para
seems like it's automatically time to
tanto parece que es ya automáticamente a
test all of this
probar todos los comportamientos de este
man's behavior throughout his entire life,
señor a lo largo de toda su vida
totally totally Like that, it's black or
totalmente totalmente Así es blanco o
white and it's like, not everything that
negro y es como no a mí todo lo que haya
this man has done throughout his life,
hecho este señor a lo largo de su vida
even the gesture itself, which was the same
Incluso el propio gesto que fue el mismo
day next to the queen, start
día al lado de la reina ponerte a
grabbing your balls, forgive me for the
cogerte las pelotas perdonarme por la
expression, but he did it like that, man, it
expresión pero lo hizo así hombre a mí
seems to me to be a person who, at the very
me parece ser una persona que como
least, totally has a lot of education to have been
mínimo total mucha Educación para llevar
in the media for as long as he has
tanto tiempo en los medios como lleva
because he is a media personality, he is the
porque es una persona mediática es el
president And look And look, there's a
presidente Y fíjate Y fíjate hay una
girl, I think it was Tamara Ramos, if I'm not
chica creo que era Tamara Ramos si no me
mistaken, I don't remember, I don't know if I'm
equivoco no me acuerdo no sé si estoy
confusing a name and surname, who
confundiendo un nombre y apellidos que
reported him and who has gone on
le denunció y que ha ido por explotados
television to tell her story with
de televisión a contar su historia con
him, I think it was a
él Creo que era una directora de
marketing director who worked with him for a few
marketing que trabajó con en algunos
years  Also she said no, even
años que además contó no que incluso
when she said that she was pregnant
cuando contó que ella estaba embarazada
no and that she was going to take I don't know if she was going to take maternity leave
no y que iba a cogerse no sé si la baja
and such that she told Rubiales who I
y tal que ella le comentó a rubiales que
think was her boss at the time
creo que era su jefe en ese momento de
please
por favor
keep this matter discreet that I have
mantenme este tema con discreción que
n't communicated it yet and such and he
todavía no lo he comunicado y tal y él
played several tricks on her that made her
le hizo varias jugarretas que se le hizo
feel very bad Well look, I don't believe that
pasar muy mal Pues fíjate que yo esa
person who was telling it
persona que lo estaba contando me la
And what happened with him there are things
creo no Y eso que pasó con él hay cosas
that I believe or I can believe or not and I
que me creo o me puedo creer o no y me
can believe about this person who is the
puedo creer de esta persona que es de la
last one that I would trust but if
última que yo me fiaría pero si
we analyze in itself what is being
analizamos en sí qué es lo que se está
put in the public pillory the issue
poniendo en la picota pública el tema
of the peak and the issue of the matter with
del pico y el tema del asunto con
Jennifer beautiful that is what is being
Jennifer hermoso que es de lo que se
talked about and is what is being
está hablando y es de lo que se está
complained about not that the
quejando no de que se está desviando el
issue of the World Cup is being diverted with this that is I repeat
tema del mundial con esto que son repito
the media what they are doing it for
los medios lo que lo están haciendo por
pure morbidity and pure politics and
por puro morbo y por pura política y por
pure Well that diverts the focus from the
pura Pues eso desviar el foco de los
important issues because for me this issue
temas importantes porque a mí este tema
is true It generates me Well yes it generates me
es verdad Me genera me Pues sí me genera
let's call it  morbid like the rest of
vamos a llamarlo morbo como al resto de
the Spanish that I put it on and sometimes I have to
los españoles que me lo pongo y a veces
take it off because I
que lo tengo que quitar porque es que
say I can't believe what I'm
digo no me puedo creer lo que estoy
reading I read things on social networks from
leyendo Leo cosas en redes sociales de
colleagues of journalists of people
de compañeros de periodistas de gente
who out of pure interest
que por puro interés
that I would like to know how
que me gustaría a mí saber cómo actúan
they act in their lives or what they do or what they
ellos en sus vidas o lo que hacen o lo
stop doing they put the typical
que dejan de hacer ponen el típico tweet
populist demagogic tweet the typical easy tweet
populista demagogo el típico tweet fácil
not that always say Jenny we are
no que siempre decir Jenny estamos
with you of seeing an English team with the
contigo de ver a un equipo inglés con la
flag Jenny without having any idea of ​​the
bandera Jenny sin tener ni idea del
context of the history of what is
contexto de la historia de lo que hay
beyond or Atlético de Madrid Jenny
más allá o el Atlético de Madrid Jenny
we are all But what is this but what is this
todas somos Pero qué es esto pero qué es
the sport but the sport of
el deporte pero el deporte de los
horses
caballos
is said ok Not
se dice ok No
that of horses that there is not going to be
el de los caballos que que ahí no se va
done how are you going to say hockey the
a hacer cómo se va a decir hockey el
sport the horses the jockeys Ok not
deporte los caballos los jinetes Ok no
with h but with Oh how was it where Look
con h sino con Ay cómo era donde Mira me
people are going to put it to me in the
lo va a poner la gente en los
comments the Polo the polo No the polo It did
comentarios el Polo el polo No el polo
n't say hockey in the in the tweet that I
No ponía hockey en el en el tweet que yo
saw it said hockey with a j in yours from Wall
vi ponía hockey con j en el tuyo de Wall
Street Wolverine and pica there has
Street Wolverine y pica
been another championship I already tell you
ha habido otro campeonato yo ya os digo
or so I am  that the most
o sea yo es que de deporte lo más
rounded sports thing I've seen are the
Redondo que he visto son las croquetas
Mara croquettes I repeat it there
del Mara lo vuelvo a repetir ahí
but who, as a guest,
pero quién invitada
prefers some croquettes or a pico some
prefiere unas croquetas o un pico unas
croquettes and well when are you going to understand
croquetas y bueno cuando vas a entender
when when you see the Mara ones When you
cuando cuando veas las del Mara Cuando
understand the Mara ones you're going to understand
entiendas las del Mara lo vas a entender
listen to me let's see it's that I do
escúchame a ver
n't know exactly what it
es que no sé exactamente qué es lo que
was but it was like the owner of something
era pero era como la dueña de algo
in the Championship When the
dentro del Campeonato Cuando gana el
boy wins, he grabs her face I
muchacho le le coge la cara visto el
saw the video I saw the video I saw the video
vídeo he visto el vídeo he visto el
this weekend and it
vídeo este mismo fin de semana y
only went viral a little bit
solamente se viralizado un poquito el
but because of the people who
vídeo pero por el tema de la gente que
are comparing it, hockey is the one
lo está comparando hockey es el que
riding the horse Javi okay forgive me
monta el caballo Javi vale perdonarme
that I'm super ignorant about sports
que yo de deporte súper cateto súper
okay But they're only bringing out the video
ignorante vale Pero el vídeo solamente
to compare it with
lo están sacando por compararlo con lo
Rubiales otherwise that video and in the
de rubiales que si no ese vídeo y en
whole world Nobody is talking about that
todo el mundo Nadie está hablando de ese
kiss which is exactly the same but you
beso que es exactamente lo mismo pero
know what happens I think that in
sabes lo que pasa que yo creo que en el
Rubiales' case it's because it's him and because of
caso de rubiales es porque es él y por
what he drags I mean there are a lot of
lo que arrastra O sea que hay mucha
people who wanted to get rid of him
gente que se lo quería cargar
probably With reason and this has been
probablemente Con razón y esto ha sido
like the  trigger, in other words, this government
como el detonante o sea este gobierno
is sick, but if you're a socialist,
está enfermo pero si eres socialista
then enjoy it, which is the best of all, well,
ya que disfrutes que es lo mejor de todo
protect it.
bueno protegerlo
The mother was a socialist, socialist, let's go, she
la madre era socialista socialista vamos
was and is the mother, it's her Facebook. Now
era y es la madre es su Facebook ahora
we'll talk about the mother. First, we have to
hablaremos de la madre primero tenemos
comment on something else. I don't want to say
que comentar otra cosa no quiero decir
one thing about that, which
una cosa con respecto a eso que me
seems a little bit to me,
parece un poco
in short, the mother is super socialist,
en resumen la madre es súper socialista
this lady, who puts a lot of
de esta señora que ponen un montón de
things in favor of Pedro Sánchez and the
cosas a favor de Pedro Sánchez y del
PSOE. Well, here, enjoy it, that's
psoe Pues toma Disfrútalo botado que esa
the ideology that yesterday,
es la ideología que este ayer antes de
before going to the intervention, I
antes de irme a la intervención
recorded a video at 7 in the morning on my
grabé un vídeo a las 7 de la mañana
way to the clinic. I recorded a
yendo camino de la clínica grabé un
video with a preview, but then I couldn't
vídeo con un adelanto pero luego no pude
broadcast what was the already leaked video.
emitir lo que era el vídeo ya filtrado
Okay, in the good one,
vale en el bueno
the thumbnail I put the frame that
que la miniatura puse el fotograma que
Albice published with her posing with the
publicó albice con ella posando con la
photo of The meme, but are you going to put the
foto de El meme pero vas a poner el
whole video? No, because there are people.
vídeo entero no porque es que hay gente
Ah, but sometimes I've seen it in some
el Ah pero a veces lo he visto en unos
places, I've seen it longer and in others
sitios lo he visto más largo y en otros
shorter. Well, now I'll explain.
más corto Bueno ahora te explico Es que
Yesterday she called me when I was leaving the clinic, she
ayer me llamó cuando salía de la clínica
called me, my name is Roma.  Gallardo by the
me llamaba me llamo Roma Gallardo que
way I finally brought it to you
por cierto por fin os lo he traído
ma'am you've been asking me for it a lot and look it came
señora que me lo pedíais mucho y mira
up the other day and you brought Roma
surgió el otro día y os traes a Roma
Gallardo whoever hasn't seen it look for
Gallardo el que no lo haya visto buscar
what's here the day before yesterday okay I
lo que está aquí antes de ayer vale me
brought Roma Gallardo the other day and yesterday
traje Roma Gallardo el otro día y ayer
when I left the clinic Roma called me He
cuando salí de la clínica me llama Roma
said to me To get on a live stream with him
Me dice Para subirme a un directo con él
or something like that he was going to do a live stream
o algo así que iba a hacer un directo
tracking the full video that they were going to
rastreando el vídeo completo que lo iban
publish it and such no To get on a
a publicar y tal no Para subirme un
live stream with him and I said Roma well
directo con él y le digo Roma pues
depending on how I feel I don't know if I'll
depende cómo me encuentre no sé si
open or if not I'll record a video with my
abriré o si no grabo yo un vídeo con el
phone or whatever right now I'm
móvil o lo que sea ahora mismo Estoy
fine So I think so and after
bien Así que creo que sí y ya después de
talking to him was when I got the blues
hablar con él fue cuando me dio tolbajón
and I had to go to bed and it's
y ya me tuve que acostar a la cama y
terrible
fatal